{
    "id": "7d9aa915b38447a5a25c46a0d272bbee",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I want to know ............................... she is angry with me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "why",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dcfcb0fd50864dc9aa0b630e0d3d0ab7"
        },
        {
            "question": "If he had asked me, I .................................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would help",
                "would have helped",
                "will help"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ff219b8826934cf890f8d576adf7860f"
        },
        {
            "question": "She would have come if you ................................... her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "invited",
                "had invited",
                "invite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "01515194388a4d51a78c4f157ca0c7e8"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are looking forward .................................... from you.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to hear",
                "to hearing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "76039aeb376c45b1aef5119f604cfbf1"
        },
        {
            "question": "No sooner did we hear the gunshots than we .................................. to the camp.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rushed",
                "rush",
                "have rushed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dcf2f2f6bac84197bbb2dc6e03df8fab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you mind ........................................ a bit?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to move",
                "moving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eb17351d64814d57ac597d46f0f58d6a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very fond ...................................... her grandchildren.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3a14995b1c8043d298e23c51d922256c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He enjoys ..................................... in the sea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "swimming",
                "to swim"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e74f3b39604d40ed94ec0c1c9402a593"
        },
        {
            "question": "She accused me ........................................... her dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to poison",
                "for poisoning",
                "of poisoning"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7dabe97ee8bd426b86ece20bc54929b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is very confident …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to win",
                "of winning",
                "about winning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "985c0bbfd18c4d55bc110401ac5e738b"
        }
    ]
}